hey guys somebody requested that I
solved this one my last two videos were
pretty intense so I thought we would do
a lighter one so we're trying to solve
for this question mark So this hundred
and this angle right here have to add to
180 so that's going to be 80 degrees and
same thing is going on down here this
110 and this has to be 180 so this will
be 70 degrees so now we have a triangle
here so 70 plus 40 plus blank has to
equal 180. that's going to be 70 degrees
so we can plug in 70 here and then by
vertical angles this is also 70. and now
we have another triangle with our
question mark it says 80 plus 70 plus
blank has to equal 180 and the blank is
going to be 30 and that means our
question mark is equal to 30. how
exciting